Guide to the J. Walter Thompson Company. Account Files, 1885-2008 and undated, bulk 1920-1995 RL.00658
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Ford Dealer Association, 1950-2007 and undated, 98 boxes
  - Visual Materials 1987-2001 and undated
    - Automobiles and Trucks
      - Focus, 1999-2000 and undated (Large format brochures removed to Oversize Materials Boxes FD-OV14 and FD-OV15.), 9 folders (Box FD65)
      - Ford full-line cars, 1993-1997, 4 folders (Box FD65)
      - Ford full-line trucks, 1994-1996, 3 folders (Box FD65)
      - Heavy-duty F-Series, 1997 (Box FD65)
      - Heavy-duty trucks, undated (Box FD65)
      - Multiple models, 1999, 2 folders (Box FD66)
      - Mustang, 1993-2000 and undated (Large format brochures removed to Oversize Materials Box FD-OV16.), 19 folders (Box FD66)
      - Pickup, chassis, 1995 (Box FD67)
      - Pickup, commercial, 1994 (Box FD67)
      - Probe, 1994-1997, 4 folders (Box FD67)
      - Ranger, 1993-2000 and undated (Large format brochures removed to Oversize Materials Box FD-OV17.), 1-4 of 28 folders (Box FD67)
      - Ranger (continued), 1993-2000 and undated, 5-28 of 28 folders (Box FD68)
      - Sport-Trac, 2000 and undated (Large format brochures removed to Oversize Materials Box FD-OV17.), 8 folders (Box FD68)
      - Taurus, 1993-2000 and undated (Large format brochures removed to Oversize Materials Boxes FD-OV18 and FD-OV19.) (Box FD69)
      - Taurus (continued) 1993-2000 and undated, 11-27 of 27 folders (Box FD70)
      - Tempo, 1993-1994, 2 folders (Box FD70)
      - Thunderbird, 1993-1997, (5 folders) (Box FD70)
      - Truck, miscellaneous, 1998, 1 of 3 folders (Box FD70)
      - Truck, miscellaneous (continued), 1998, 2-3 of 3 folders (Box FD71)
      - Van, commercial, 1994, 2 folders (Box FD71)
      - Windstar, 1996-2000 (Large format brochures removed to Oversize Materials Box FD-OV19.), 13 folders (Box FD71)
      - [ZX2, 2000: Removed to Oversize Materials Box FD-OV19.] (Box FD71)
      - Transparencies catalog information (paper records), 1997, 2 folders (Box FD72)
      - Miscellaneous and unlabeled automotive images, 2000 and undated, 11 folders (Box FD72)
    - District and Regional FDA's
      - Buffalo, undated, 2 folders (Box FD73)
      - Buffalo, Chicago, St. Louis, circa 1980s-1990s (Box FD73)
      - Central Indiana, undated (Box FD73)
      - Chicago, undated (Large format presentation materials removed to Oversize Materials Box FD-OV20.), 3 folders (Box FD73)
      - Cincinnati, undated (Box FD73)
      - Cleveland, undated, 3 folders (Box FD73)
      - Columbus, undated (Box FD73)
      - Erie, 1989 (Box FD73)
      - Hawaii, undated (Box FD73)
      - Houston, 1987-1988 and undated, 5 folders (Box FD73)
      - Indianapolis, undated, 1-3 of 5 folders (Box FD73)
      - Indianapolis (continued), undated, 4-5 of 5 folders (Box FD74)
      - Middle America, undated (Box FD74)
      - Milwaukee, undated (Large format presentation materials removed to Oversize Materials Box FD-OV20.), 3 folders (Box FD74)
      - Newark, 1988-1989 and undated, 2 folders (Box FD74)
      - New England, undated (Box FD74)
      - New Orleans FDA presentation, 1989 (Box FD74)
      - Northeast Ohio, undated (Box FD74)
      - Northwest Ohio (Toledo), undated (Box FD74)
      - Philadelphia, undated (Box FD74)
      - Regional Advertising Force presentation, 2000, 4 folders (Box FD74)
      - Rochester, 1988 and undated, 2 folders (Box FD74)
      - San Jose, 1989 (Box FD75)
      - South Florida FDA staff photographs, 2000 (Box FD75)
      - Southern Virginia, undated (Box FD75)
      - St. Louis, 1990 and undated, 2 folders (Box FD75)
      - Twin Cities, undated (Box FD75)
      - Virginia-Carolina, undated (Box FD75)
      - Youngstown, Ohio, undated (Box FD75)
    - Drawings and Sketches
      - Contour, undated (Box FD75)
      - Crown Victoria, undated (Box FD75)
      - Escort, 1997 and undated, 2 folders (Box FD75)
      - Expedition, undated (Box FD75)
      - Explorer, undated (Box FD75)
      - F-150, undated (Box FD75)
      - Generic print advertisement mockup, undated (Box FD75)
      - Mustang, undated (Box FD75)
      - Probe, undated (Box FD75)
      - Ranger, undated (Box FD75)
      - Taurus, undated (Box FD75)
      - Texas Truck Month, undated (Box FD75)
      - Thunderbird, undated (Box FD75)
      - Windstar, undated (Box FD75)
      - Miscellaneous sketches, undated (Box FD75)
    - Logos and Miscellaneous Images
      - Ad Planner badges, 2000 (Box FD75)
      - [Auto Link graphics, undated: Removed to Oversize Materials Box FD-OV20] (Box FD75)
      - Color chips, 1998-2001 and undated (Box FD75)
      - [Contact sheets, campaign with Toby Keith, undated: Removed to Oversize Materials Box FD-OV20] (Box FD75)
      - Dealer World Magazine, undated (Box FD75)
      - Factory Authorized Clearance, undated (Box FD75)
      - FDAF bugs, undated (Box FD75)
      - Festiva jewelry, undated (Box FD75)
      - [Firestone safety advertisement, 2000: Removed to Oversize Materials Box FD-OV20.] (Box FD75)
      - Ford Annual Clearance, undated (Box FD75)
      - Ford Funding, undated (Box FD75)
      - [Ford Introduction Show, 1997: Removed to Oversize Materials] (Box FD75)
      - Ford logos, 1988 and undated, 5 folders (Box FD76)
      - Ford painted sign on wall, undated (Box FD76)
      - Ford Preferred, undated (Box FD76)
      - Ford Quality of Life, undated (Box FD76)
      - Ford Quality People, Quality Products, undated (Box FD76)
      - Ford Truck and Pylon slides, undated (Box FD76)
      - Ford Trucks, undated, 2 folders (Box FD76)
      - Historic advertisements for Ford/JWT 50th anniversary book, circa 1994 (Box FD76)
      - Hot You're Hot, undated (Box FD76)
      - JWT/FDAF promotional flare gun photograph, undated (Box FD76)
      - [Location shots, 1996 and undated: Removed to Oversize Materials Box FD-OV20.] (Box FD76)
      - Motor Trend Car of the Year (Box FD76)
      - Pickup trucks, 1992 (Box FD76)
        [Billy Robin McFarland slides of Twin Cities assembly plant]
      - [Program designs, JWT/FDAF Chairman's Meeting, 1993: Removed to Oversize Materials Box FD-OV20.] (Box FD76)
      - Regional Advertising Group, undated (Box FD76)
      - Showroom of the Future, undated (Box FD76)
      - [Storyboard--California Action Heroes, 1997: Removed to Oversize Materials Box FD-OV20.] (Box FD76)
      - Warranty stickers, undated (Box FD76)
      - [Window sticker designs, 2002: Removed to Oversize Materials Box FD-OV20.] (Box FD76)
      - Winning the World Over, undated (Box FD76)
      - Miscellaneous and unlabeled automotive images, undated, 5 folders (Box FD76)
      - FDAF tie pin (artifact), undated (Box FD76)
  - Oversize Materials 1961-2007 and undated
    [Contains large format items removed from previous series.]
    - General
      - Account management--miscellaneous charts, 1961-1994 and undated (Box FD-OV1)
      - Clippings, 1978-2007, 5 folders (Box FD-OV1)
      - Correspondence, 1979-1981 (Box FD-OV1)
      - Export Sales Marketing Planner, 1995 (Box FD-OV1)
      - Meetings, JWT/FDAF, 1986 (Box FD-OV1)
      - Printed material (Auto show, 1976 Armchair Estimator), 1962, 1976 (Box FD-OV1)
    - Promotional campaigns
      - Are You Letting Willys Hook the Big Profits?, 1961 (Box FD-OV2)
      - Big Truck Throw Down (with Toby Keith), undated (Box FD-OV2)
      - Blue Chip Security, 1983 (Box FD-OV2)
      - Bold Moves, undated (Box FD-OV2)
      - Ford-Approved Accessories (Australia), undated (Box FD-OV2)
      - Ford/Coca-Cola tie-in (Texas Sweepstakes), undated (Box FD-OV2)
      - Fusion Challenge, undated (Box FD-OV2)
      - Great American Sales Event, 1994 (Box FD-OV2)
      - Here Come the '68 Job Tamers, 1967 (Box FD-OV2)
      - New Ford Ranger (English and Spanish), undated (Box FD-OV2)
      - Texas, Ford and You, undated (Box FD-OV2)
      - Miscellaneous truck promotions, 1972 and undated (Box FD-OV2)
    - Sample advertisements
      - Outdoor, circa 1970s (Box FD-OV3)
      - Point-of-Purchase
        - Banners, 2006 and undated (Box FD-OV3)
        - Displays--Edge, Focus, 2006 (Box FD-OV4)
        - Displays (continued)--Expedition, Freestyle, Five Hundred, 2007 (Box FD-OV5)
        - Hang tags, posters, undated (Box FD-OV6)
      - Print Medium (Box FD-OV7)
        - Ad Planner, 1991-1995, 5 folders (Box FD-OV7)
        - Cars and trucks, 1979-2004 and undated (Box FD-OV7)
        - Corporate advertising, 1982-2000 and undated (Box FD-OV7)
        - Dealer promotions and sales events, 1979-1991 and undated (Box FD-OV7)
        - Ford Asia-Pacific and Africa, 2005 (Box FD-OV7)
        - Ford Turkey, 1990s (Box FD-OV7)
        - Newspaper, 1979-2003 (Box FD-OV7)
    - Visual Materials
      - Automobiles and Trucks
        - Capri, Tracer, 1993 (Box FD-OV8)
        - Commercial trucks, 1996 (Box FD-OV8)
        - Contour, 1998, 2000 (Box FD-OV8)
        - Crown Victoria, 2000 (Box FD-OV8)
        - Econoline Club Wagon, 2000 (Box FD-OV9)
        - Escape, 2000 (Box FD-OV9)
        - Escort, 1998, 2000 and undated (Box FD-OV9)
        - Excursion, 2000 (Box FD-OV10)
        - Expedition, 1997, 2000 and undated (Box FD-OV11)
        - Explorer (includes Sport Trac), 2000-2001 (Box FD-OV12)
        - F-150, 2000 (Box FD-OV13)
        - F-250, 2000 (Box FD-OV13)
        - F-350, 2000 (Box FD-OV13)
        - Focus, 1999-2000 (Box FD-OV14)
        - Focus (continued), 2000 (Box FD-OV15)
        - Mustang, 1998, 2000 (Box FD-OV16)
        - Ranger, 1997-2000 (Box FD-OV17)
        - Sport-Trac, 2000 (Box FD-OV17)
        - Taurus, 2000 (Box FD-OV18)
        - Taurus (continued), 2000 (Box FD-OV19)
        - Windstar, 2000 (Box FD-OV19)
        - ZX2, 2000 (Box FD-OV19)
      - Miscellaneous
        - 75 Years with Ford, dealer award, 1992 (Box FD-OV20)
        - Auto Link graphics, undated (Box FD-OV20)
        - Chicago FDA, pins, pylon designs, undated (Box FD-OV20)
        - Contact sheets--Campaign with Toby Keith, undated (Box FD-OV20)
        - Firestone safety advertisement, 2000 (Box FD-OV20)
        - Ford Introduction Show, 1997 (Box FD-OV20)
        - Location shots, 1996 and undated (Box FD-OV20)
        - Logos and lettering designs, 1991 and undated (Box FD-OV20)
        - Logos, Asia Pacific Ford Dealers, undated (Box FD-OV20)
        - Milwaukee FDA graphics, undated (Box FD-OV20)
        - Program designs, JWT/FDA Chairman's Meeting, 1993 (Box FD-OV20)
        - Regional Advertising Force--Bob McClowry photograph, undated (Box FD-OV20)
        - Storyboard--California Action Heroes, 1997 (Box FD-OV20)
        - Window sticker designs, 2002 (Box FD-OV20)
      - Presentation transparencies, circa 1990 (Box FD-OV21)
    - Restricted Oversize Materials
      - Account Management--Miscellaneous charts, 1990s-2006 (Box FD-OV22)
      - Promotional Campaigns--Big Truck Throwdown, 2004 (Box FD-OV22)
      - Promotional Campaigns--Blue's Clues, 2001 (Box FD-OV22)
      - Promotional Campaigns--Bold Moves, 2006 (Box FD-OV22)
      - Promotional Campaigns--Brand Alliance/Sponsorship planning, 2000, 2002 (Box FD-OV22)
      - Promotional Campaigns--RAF Canada mailer, 2002 (Box FD-OV22)
      - Promotional Campaigns--Toolbox refills, 2000-2001 (Box FD-OV22)
    - Oversize Folders
      - Cars and Trucks--Explorer, 2002 (Box FD-OV22, Folder FD1)
      - Cars and Trucks--Focus, undated (Box FD-OV22, Folder FD2)
      - Cars and Trucks--Miscellaneous, 2000 and undated (Box FD-OV22, Folder FD3)
      - Cars and Trucks--Miscellaneous, 1998, 2000 and undated (Folder FD4)
        - (Includes Batmobile Chassis advertisement.) (Box FD-OV22)
      - Cars and Trucks--Taurus catalog, 2000 (Box FD-OV22, Folder FD5)
      - Creative--Promotional Campaigns--Bright Future campaign, undated (Box FD-OV22, Folder FD6-13)
      - Creative--Promotional Campaigns--Ford Country trucks promotion, undated (Box FD-OV22, Folder FD14-15)
      - Creative--Promotional Campaigns--Internet Birthday Card Giveaway, undated (Box FD-OV22, Folder FD16)
      - Creative--Promotional Campaigns--Komen Race for the Cure, 2000 (Box FD-OV22, Folder FD17)
      - Creative--Promotional Campaigns--Nascar, 2000 and undated (Box FD-OV22, Folder FD18-19)
      - Creative--Promotional Campaigns--Toys for Tots display and jazz poster, 2000 (Box FD-OV22, Folder FD20)
      - Regional FDA--Northwest Ohio, undated (Box FD-OV22, Folder FD21)
      - Creative--Promotional Campaigns--No Boundaries campaign, undated
        - (Includes large posters rolled into oversize tube.) (Box FD-OV22)
- Ford Audiovisual Materials, 1956-2006 and undated [RESTRICTED]
  Includes VHS, Umatic and Betacam videocassettes, audiocassettes and CD-R's documenting domestic, international, and global advertising campaigns; advertisement compilations; historical advertising; and presentations. Arranged alphabetically by subject area.
  [Restrictions on access: Audiovisual materials are closed to patrons until use copies can be made.]
  - Ad Planner, images and artwork, 2000-2003 and undated. Format: CD-R, 21 discs (Box FM-AV1)
  - Argentina (Box FM-AV2)
    - 1,2,3 Ford, 2001. TRT: 0:44. Format: VHS-NTSC (Box FM-AV2)
    - Argentina Rally podium shot, 1993. TRT: 5:00. Format: Betacam SP (Box FM-AV2)
    - BE 146 (KA), 1996. TRT: 60:00. Format: VHS-NTSC (Box FM-AV2)
    - BE 146 training version, undated. TRT: 20:00. Format: Umatic (Box FM-AV2)
    - Comerciales, 2001. TRT: 120:00. Format: VHS-NTSC (Box FM-AV2)
    - Comerciales (F100 old, Fiesta, KA, F100 new), undated. TRT: 120:00. Format: VHS-NTSC (Box FM-AV2)
    - Commercials, 2001. TRT: 10:00. Format: Umatic (Box FM-AV2)
    - Commercials, undated. TRT: 10:00. Format: Umatic (Box FM-AV2)
    - Commercials, undated. TRT: 10:00. Format: Umatic (Box FM-AV2)
    - Creative Show, 1998. TRT: 120:00. Format: VHS-NTSC (Box FM-AV2)
    - Escort, Aero Puerto/Desfile, undated. TRT: 5:00. Format: Umatic (Box FM-AV3)
    - Escort, Dentista/Jaimito, undated. TRT: 10:00. Format: Umatic (Box FM-AV3)
    - Escort/KA/Fiesta/F-100, undated. TRT: 120:00. Format: VHS-NTSC (Box FM-AV3)
    - F-100, 25th Anniversary TVC, undated. TRT: 120:00. Format: VHS-NTSC (Box FM-AV3)
    - F-100, Caso F-100, 1999. TRT: 20:00. Format: Umatic (Box FM-AV3)
    - F-100, Hercules/Zamba/50 Years, undated. TRT: 10:00. Format: Umatic (Box FM-AV3)
    - F-100, Hercules ii/Making of/Apertura CQC, undated. TRT: 60:00. Format: Umatic (Box FM-AV3)
    - Falcon/KA, undated. TRT: 20:00. Format: Umatic (Box FM-AV3)
    - Fiesta, Patota/Chocador, undated. TRT: 120:00. Format: VHS-PAL (Box FM-AV3)
    - Focus, 1999. TRT: 20:00. Format: Umatic (Box FM-AV4)
    - Focus, Caballeros, 2001. TRT: 10:00. Format: Umatic (Box FM-AV4)
    - Focus, Horizonte/Expect More, 1993. TRT: 10:00. Format: Umatic (Box FM-AV4)
    - Ford 2001, 2001. TRT: 120:00. Format: VHS-NTSC (Box FM-AV4)
    - Historical reel, 1990-1994. TRT: 10:00. Format: Umatic (Box FM-AV4)
    - KA, Abri tu mente, undated. TRT: 0:45. Format: Umatic (Box FM-AV4)
    - KA, Equipment, undated. TRT: 120:00. Format: VHS-NTSC (Box FM-AV4)
    - KA, Libelula (Dragonfly), 2001. TRT: 120:00. Format: VHS-NTSC (Box FM-AV4)
    - KA, Piano, untitled. TRT: 120:00. Format: VHS-NTSC (Box FM-AV4)
    - KA, Subtitulado, undated. TRT: 10:00. Format: Umatic (Box FM-AV4)
    - KA/Fiesta/Escort/Ranger, undated. TRT: 120:00. Format: VHS-NTSC (Box FM-AV4)
    - Mondeo, Dropping, undated. TRT: 10:00. Format: Umatic (Box FM-AV5)
    - Movil Gap, 1999. TRT: 15:00. Format: Audiocassette (Box FM-AV5)
    - Nueva F-100. Solo Ford podia reinventar la pickup, undated. TRT: 30:00. Format: VHS (Box FM-AV5)
    - Outfitters, 1999. TRT: 30:00. Format: VHS-NTSC (Box FM-AV5)
    - Programas, 1999. TRT: 120:00. Format: VHS-NTSC (Box FM-AV5)
    - Ranger, undated. TRT: 90:00. Format: Betacam SP (Box FM-AV5)
    - Ranger, Power Stroke, 2001. TRT: 120:00. Format: VHS (Box FM-AV5)
    - Various commercials, 2000. TRT: 20:00. Format: Betacam SP (Box FM-AV5)
    - Various commercials, undated. TRT: 120:00. Format: VHS-NTSC (Box FM-AV5)
    - Video Outfitters, 2001. TRT: 120:00. Format: VHS-NTSC (Box FM-AV5)
  - Asia-Pacific compilation reel, 1999-2000. TRT: 10:00. Format: Betacam SP (Box FM-AV5)
  - Australia (Melbourne) (Box FM-AV6)
    - Built Ford Tough, 2001. TRT: 5:00. Format: VHS-NTSC (Box FM-AV6)
    - Compilation--19TVC's, 1995. TRT: 30:00. Format: VHS (Box FM-AV6)
    - Compilation, 1996. TRT: 9:06. Format: Umatic (Box FM-AV6)
    - Compilation, 1997. TRT: 22:00. Format: Umatic (Box FM-AV6)
    - Compilation, 1997. TRT: 6:00. Format: Umatic (Box FM-AV6)
    - Compilation--4 TVC's, 1998. TRT: 10:00. Format: Umatic (Box FM-AV6)
    - Compilation--10 TVC's (NTSC), 1999. TRT: 10:00. Format: Umatic (Box FM-AV6)
    - Compilation--17 TVC's (NTSC), 2000. TRT: 20:00. Format: Umatic (Box FM-AV6)
    - Compilation--46 TVC's, 2000. TRT: 25:00. Format: Betacam SP (Box FM-AV6)
    - Compilation--49 TVC's, 2000. TRT: 36:00. Format: Betacam SP (Box FM-AV7)
    - Compilation of Motor Vehicle Shots, 1999-2001. TRT: 120:00. Format: VHS-NTSC (Box FM-AV7)
    - Corporate--Live It campaign, 1999. TRT: 5:00. Format: Umatic (Box FM-AV7)
    - Corporate--Live It campaign, 1999. TRT: 20:00. Format: Umatic (Box FM-AV7)
    - Corporate--Live It campaign, undated. TRT: 30:00. Format: VHS-NTSC (Box FM-AV7)
    - Corporate--Live It sendups, undated. TRT: 60:00. Format: VHS-NTSC (Box FM-AV7)
    - Corporate--Totally Full Frontal/Live It sendups, 1999. TRT: 10:00. Format: Umatic (Box FM-AV7)
    - Courier Turbo Diesel, 1999. TRT: 4:31. Format: VHS-NTSC (Box FM-AV7)
    - Courier radio spots, 1999. TRT: 2:00. Format: Audiocassette (Box FM-AV7)
    - Courier Turbo Diesel, 1999. TRT: 3:00. Format: VHS (Box FM-AV7)
    - Explorer, The Chase, 2000. TRT: 0:30. Format: Umatic (Box FM-AV7)
    - FDAF Chairman's quotes, undated. TRT: 5:00. Format: Umatic (Box FM-AV8)
    - FDAF compilation 19 TVC's, 1998. TRT: 30:00. Format: Umatic (Box FM-AV8)
    - Ford in Your Face, 1998. TRT: 5:00. Format: VHS (Box FM-AV8)
    - Historical reel, 1995. TRT: 60:00. Format: Umatic (Box FM-AV8)
    - Just Squeezed, 1995. TRT: 0:30. Format: Umatic (Box FM-AV8)
    - Laser, Streetwise spot, undated. TRT: 1:00. Format: VHS (Box FM-AV8)
    - Primary brand campaign, 2001. TRT: 8:00. Format: VHS-NTSC (Box FM-AV8)
    - TVC's April through June, 1995. TRT: 10:00. Format: Umatic (Box FM-AV8)
    - Various TVS's, 1997. TRT: 55:00. Format: Umatic (Box FM-AV8)
  - Badges (images), 1999-2000 and undated. Format: CD-R, 2 discs (Box FM-AV9)
  - Big as Life, undated. TRT: 10:00. Format: Umatic (Box FM-AV9)
  - Billboard renders (Taurus, Explorer), 2003. Format: CD-R (Box FM-AV9)
  - Black White and Color, undated. Format: CD (Box FM-AV9)
  - Bold Moves (Mustang), 2006. Format: DVD, 2 copies (Box FM-AV9)
  - Bold Moves (Mustang) launch, 2006. Format: DVD (Box FM-AV9)
  - Bolivia (La Paz)
    - Creativo, 1999. Format: ZIP disc (Box FM-AV9)
    - Explorer, Dealer spots, 1998. TRT: 30:00. Format: VHS (Box FM-AV9)
    - Galindo, Hugo, TV spots, undated. TRT: 30:00. Format: VHS (Box FM-AV9)
  - Brand Essence, undated. TRT: 30:00. Format: VHS (Box FM-AV9)
  - Brazil (São Paulo) (Box FM-AV10)
    - ABRADIF--Tier 2/Dealer Tier 3 spots, 2001. TRT: 30:00. Format: VHS (Box FM-AV10)
    - ABRADIF--Top Models/Test Drive Fiesta/Diferencas, 1995. TRT: 1:30. Format: Umatic (Box FM-AV10)
    - Great Sales Ford historical reel, 1994. TRT: 60:00. Format: Umatic (Box FM-AV10)
    - KA, 1997. TRT: 5:00. Format: Umatic (Box FM-AV10)
    - Quinzena Ford/Quinzena Ford I, undated. TRT: 20:00. Format: Umatic (Box FM-AV10)
    - Show de Ofertas, 1995. TRT: 10:00. Format: Umatic (Box FM-AV10)
    - Truck commercials (Ford and competition), 1996-1998. TRT: 20:00. Format: Umatic (Box FM-AV10)
    - UAU=WOW/Let a Ford Surprise You, 2001. TRT: 10:00. Format: Umatic (Box FM-AV10)
  - Brophy, miscellaneous images, undated. Format: CD-R (Box FM-AV10)
  - California Research, 2005. TRT: 30:00. Format: Umatic (Box FM-AV10)
  - Canada (Box FM-AV11)
    - Branding Night in Canada/Hockey Night in Canada, 2000. TRT: 10:00. Format: VHS (Box FM-AV11)
    - Compilation reel (Ford, Ford Corporate, Mazda, Jaguar), undated. TRT: 30:00. Format: VHS (Box FM-AV11)
    - Images, 2002. Format: CD-R, 17 discs (Box FM-AV11)
    - Images, 2002 and undated. Format: DVD-R, 3 discs (Box FM-AV11)
    - J. Walter Thompson has been helping Ford Dealers sell more cars and trucks for over 57 years, circa 2002. TRT: 30:00. Format: VHS, 2 tapes (Box FM-AV11)
    - J. Walter Thompson has been helping sell products in Canada for over 72 years, circa 2002. TRT: 30:00. Format: VHS, 2 tapes (Box FM-AV11)
    - Pitch materials, 2002 and undated. Format: DVD-R, 7 discs (Box FM-AV11)
    - Various spots, 1999. TRT: 10:00. Format: VHS (Box FM-AV11)
  - Caribbean/Central America (Box FM-AV12)
    - Primary Brand Positioning Campaign, 2000. TRT: 10:00. Format: Betacam SP (Box FM-AV12)
    - Primary Brand Positioning Campaign, 2000. Format: CD (Box FM-AV12)
    - Primary Brand Positioning Campaign, 2000. TRT: 10:00. Format: VHS (Box FM-AV12)
  - Chile (Santiago)
    - Automora Del Pacifico (Reel Ford, Contour, Fiesta, Ranger XLT), 1995. TRT: 10:00. Format: Umatic (Box FM-AV12)
    - Compilation reel, 1995. TRT: 60:00. Format: Umatic (Box FM-AV12)
    - Fiesta, 1995. TRT: 10:00. Format: Umatic (Box FM-AV12)
    - Pacific Automotive, undated. TRT: 5:00. Format: VHS (Box FM-AV12)
    - Programas 14-17, undated. TRT: 10:00. Format: VHS (Box FM-AV12)
  - China (Beijing) (Box FM-AV13)
    - Shanghai Auto Show, 1996. TRT: 4:22. Format: Betacam SP (Box FM-AV13)
  - Communications Trading Company, Ford KA spot, 1996. TRT: 10:00. Format: Umatic (Box FM-AV13)
  - Compilation reel (Excursion, Lincoln Blackwood, Ford P2000 Hydrogen Fuel Cell, Aston Martin DB7, Historical Jaguar, Mazda Racing), 2000. TRT: 60:00. Format: Umatic (Box FM-AV13)
  - Contour/Mystique spots, undated. TRT: 5:00. Format: VHS (Box FM-AV13)
  - Cosmopolitan and Ford Talk to Women, undated. TRT: 30:00. Format: VHS (Box FM-AV13)
  - Crown Victoria images, 2003. Format: CD-R (Box FM-AV13)
  - Detroit--Dealership sales events advertisements, 1996-2000. TRT: 10:00. Format: VHS (Box FM-AV13)
  - Digital Help, unidentified images, undated. Format: CD-R (Box FM-AV13)
  - Direct Approach Generic, 1992. TRT: 0:30. Format: 1" video (Box FM-AV13)
  - Dubai (Box FM-AV14)
    - Ben Sulaym racing highlights, 1997-1998. TRT: 120:00. Format: VHS (Box FM-AV14)
    - Crown Victoria, all edits, undated. TRT: 120:00. Format: VHS (Box FM-AV14)
    - Crown Victoria/Grand Marquis/Ranger/Mercury, 1999. TRT: 10:00. Format: VHS (Box FM-AV14)
    - Crown Victoria, Scout spot, 1999. TRT: 30:00. Format: Betacam SP (Box FM-AV14)
    - Crown Victoria, Stays With You/Family Showdown, undated. TRT: 120:00. Format: VHS (Box FM-AV14)
    - Escort (Jordan, Lebanon, Qatar), 1998. TRT: 30:00. Format: Betacam SP (Box FM-AV14)
    - Expedition/Ranger, 1999. TRT: 30:00. Format: Betacam SP (Box FM-AV14)
    - Focus MBS edits, Arabic, undated. TRT: 0:30. Format: VHS (Box FM-AV14)
    - Grand Marquis, Arabic, 1999. TRT: 0:45. Format: Betacam SP (Box FM-AV14)
    - Grand Marquis, Success spot, 1999. TRT: 1:00. Format: VHS (Box FM-AV14)
    - Historical showreel, 1993-1994. TRT: 60:00. Format: Umatic (Box FM-AV14)
    - Mercury Divisional, undated. TRT: 120:00. Format: VHS (Box FM-AV14)
    - Ranger/Crown Victoria/Other, 1995-1999. TRT: 120:00. Format: VHS (Box FM-AV14)
    - Various TVC's, PAL, 1998. TRT: 60:00. Format: VHS-PAL (Box FM-AV14)
    - Various TVC's, PAL, 1998. TRT: 60:00. Format: Betacam SP (Box FM-AV14)
  - Escape (Box FM-AV15)
    - Billboard image, 2003. Format: CD-R (Box FM-AV15)
    - Smart Unique Versatile, undated. TRT: 10:00. Format: VHS (Box FM-AV15)
  - Escort
    - Images, 1998 and undated. Format: CD-R, 3 discs (Box FM-AV15)